in-gender.com 2017-02-27

# Privacy Policy : Ingender.com

Ingender.com does not sell, rent, or disclose in any way your personally identifiable information to any third party.

This includes your name, email address, and payment information. Your personal information will never be revealed unless personal safety is at issue, or required by law enforcement.

## Visit Tracking

As with most other websites, Ingender.com automatically logs information about users who visit the site. This includes IP address, ISP (internet service provider), browser (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), device used (such as desktop or mobile device), and pages visited. 

This information is not personally identifiable (it is not associated with your name or user account). It is stored in log files, and also transmitted to Google Analytics, for the purpose of improving, maintaining, and optimising this site.

## Site Cookies

Ingender.com uses cookies to implement some features, including logging in to your account. A _cookie_ is simply a small piece of information which is stored by your browser; your browser will only return the cookie to the site that created it. You can use the settings in your browser to delete or disable cookies, but you may not be able to use some features on the site.

## Advertising

Third party advertisements support Ingender.com. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies:** We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). 

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.

You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [doubleclick.com](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
